linelab.org 2017-11-14

# Privacy Policy

##  [ Privacy Policy](http://www.linelabox.com/privacy-policy)

Details
     Hits: 10678 

### 1\. Introduction

We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information that may be collected by us on our site.

### 2\. Types of information we collect

**Personal Data** : This is data that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you and may include your name, address, email address. Such information is only collected from you if you voluntarily submit it to us.

**Non-Personal Data** : Like most websites, we gather statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate basis of all visitors to our website. This Non-Personal Data comprises information that cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information regarding, for example, user IP addresses where they have been clipped or anonymised, browser types and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our website.

### 3\. Use of data

No information submitted by a you will be shared, sold, reused in lists, or be used for any other purpose than to complete a transaction or address a customer service concern.

### 4\. Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings but we have no access to or control over these cookies. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to our site.

### 5\. External links

When you click on a link on this web site that takes you to a web site operated by another company, you will be subjected to that company's web site privacy policies.
